http://www.airnav.com/info/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
This web site is the property of AirNav, LLC, a New Jersey Limited Liability Company.
AirNav has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy issues. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of AirNav.
At AirNav, we are very committed to your privacy, so here is our privacy promise to you.
AIRNAV PRIVACY COMMITMENT
AirNav will never sell, exchange, or release to an unaffiliated third party any of your individual personal information without your express permission.
Information we may collect
If you visit our web site: When you visit our web site, your web browser transmits to our server(s) some basic information needed to complete your request: your IP address, the page you request, any parameters for the request, the browser you are using (including version and operating system,) and the page you are coming from.
This information is used to serve your request for a web page, and some of it is then kept in our web server logs.
If you register to obtain an AirNav user ID: When you register with AirNav to obtain a user ID and password, in addition to the information we gather from all web site visitors we also ask you to provide us with your name, your email address, your chosen user ID and password, and some basic demographic information such as you postal/zip code, your country, your home base airport, and your involvement in aviation.
We keep all this information in an encrypted form in our systems.
If you purchase products or services from us: We collect from you identification information such as your name, your company, address, telephone number, fax number, and email address.
We also keep a record of the products or services you ordered from us.
When you send us your payment we may also collect additional information such as the date of payment, your method of payment and your account number or credit card number and expiration date.
If you submit user comments: We will collect the information that you write in the comment, the date and time that you wrote your comment, and associate that information with your user ID.
If you submit any other information over the web site: We receive and record the information you submit (such as fuel price updates, business listings, etc.)
If you email us: In addition to the contents of your message, we collect your email address and the list of email servers that the message traversed on its way to us.
If you fax us: In addition to the contents of your message, we collect your fax header information and the number you called from via Caller ID.
If you write to us by mail: In addition to the contents of your message, we collect your return address and postmark date.
If you call us: In addition to the contents of your message, we collect the telephone number you are calling from via Caller ID.
How we use the information
We analyze our web logs for activity, trends, most frequently requested pages, paths through the web site, etc.
This enables us to understand how our users use our web site, and how we can improve to make it even easier to use. In our analysis we look at aggregate information, as our logs do not have any personal identifying information.
We may have a need to contact you for clarification on some submission you made, to reply to a message you sent us, to inform you of an update made to your listing, or to solicit your assistance with some issue.
We will use personal identifying information we have about you in our attempt to contact you.
If you submit a comment about a business, service, or facility listed on AirNav, and we publish your comment on our web site, we will publish also your name and the date you made your comment.
Upon request by the business affected by your comment, who may want to follow up with you regarding your comment, we may also release to the affected business personally identifying information such as your email address or home base.
If you want your name withheld from any specific comment, please contact us by email.
Be aware that after we remove your name the comment will read as coming from an anonymous person, and we will after that honor any request by anyone to remove that comment.
Occasionally, an AirNav user or other interested party may desire to contact another AirNav user.
This happens most often as a result of a comment posted by a registered user.
We will follow your instructions about release of your name and email address to any such third party.
When you register with us, or when you subsequently update your profile with us, you are given three options for protection of your email address: do not share with anybody, share only with other registered users, or share with anyone.
We will follow your instructions when dealing with requests by third parties.
From time to time, we may share with third parties aggregate information, such as how many visitors we get per day, or how many of our registered users are pilots. Such information will not contain any personal identifying information.
From time to time, we make available to third parties information in bulk, such as lists of FBOs, lists of fuel prices, etc. We will never release email addresses as part of any bulk data that we may release to a third party. We will never release personal identifying information about our registered users as part of any bulk data that we may release to any third party.
We will disclose personal identifying information we may have in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
About our partners and affiliates
AirNav partners with third parties to provide some services that are best provided in conjunction with a third party.
We may disclose your personal identifying information to these affiliated third parties as needed to provide the associated services. In addition, they may collect personal identifying information themselves, and may in some cases share it with us.
If you are interested in the privacy policies of our partners or affiliates, please visit their web sites.
Online travel reservations for AirNav are handled by Travelnow.com.
You may view their privacy policy at www.travelnow.com/index.jsp?pageName=privacy
Some car rentals are handled by Avis Rent A Car or Enterprise Rent-A-Car.
You may view their privacy policies at www.avis.com/car-rental/html/global/en/terms/privacy_policy.html and www.enterprise.com/about/privacyPolicy.html respectively
Online credit card payments to us are processed by iTransact.
You may view their privacy policy at itransact.com/about/privacy-policy
We also process some online payments using PayPal and Google Checkout. You may view their privacy policies at www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside and www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html
About external links
To improve your browsing experience on the world-wide web, our web site provides links to numerous sites and pages that are not affiliated with us in any way.
When you follow a link to such an external site, you are no longer on the AirNav web site.
We do not review or have any control over the privacy practices of those external sites.
You may have to find those privacy notices yourself.
Frequently a link to a privacy policy exists at the bottom of the main page for each site.
Use of Cookies
Like many other web sites, we make use of "cookies." Our site uses cookies to improve your interactive experience.
However, cookies are not required.
If you disable cookies in your browser our site will still work, but with a less user-friendly interactive experience.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small bits of information exchanged between your computer and ours.
We start by sending you a cookie, and your computer automatically sends it back every time you make a request for a new page.
We assign unique cookies to each session, and that enables us to maintain some memory between pages you visit &dash that way you don't have to keep entering the same information over and over.
For example, if you check the box for "Remember me" when you log in, we will place a cookie on your computer so that in the future you don't have to provide your user ID and password with every submission. If you choose not to accept our cookies that's fine with us, but you'll have to retype more often.
We do not use cookies for any other purpose other than keeping some information across page requests.
Also, speaking of cookies, you should know that AirNav's affiliates or independent sites may use their own cookies. Cookies from those sites are use for the purposes of those sites. You may want to read their privacy policies for information on how they use cookies.
We do not exchange cookie information with any third party.
If you do not want to accept cookies from AirNav or other sites, your
browser software should allow you set that preference. In Microsoft Internet Explorer look under Internet Options, in Netscape look under Preferences.
About this Privacy Policy
As conditions evolve, we may have a need to change how we handle our information. As a result, we may need to revise our Privacy Policy.
If we do, we will publish the updated policy on our web site, and we will also place a prominent notice on our web site for 30 days.
If you are concerned about how your personal identifying information is used, you should review our Privacy Policy periodically.
For further information about our privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with AirNav, please Contact us.
Copyright © AirNav, LLC. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
Contact
